Guide to the Jesus Salvador Treviño Papers M0624
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Accession 2007-192
  - Movimiento Chapters 11-19 (1 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Movimiento Chapters 11-19 (2 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Movimiento Chapters 11-19 (3 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Movimiento Chapters 11-19 (4 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chicano! Music-CD (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Chicano! Post-Prod. (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Chicano! Post-Prod. (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Chicano! History of the Mexican American Civil Rights Movement (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Chicano! History of the Mexican American Civil Rights Movement (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Chicano! History of the Mexican American Civil Rights Movement (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Chicano! History of the Mexican American Civil Rights Movement (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Chicano! Episode Scripts #1 - #4 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Chicano! Episode Scripts #1 - #4 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chicano! Episode Scripts #1 - #4 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chicano! Episode Scripts #1 - #4 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chicano! Episode Scripts #1 - #4 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chicano! CD-Rom Volume I TLCI (1 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Chicano! CD-Rom Volume I TLCI (2 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Chicano! CD-Rom Volume I TLCI (3 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chicano! CD-Rom Volume I TLCI (4 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Chicano! CD-Rom Volume I TLCI (5 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Chicano! The Book (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Chicano! CD-Rom (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Chicano! CD-Rom (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - "The Story of the Latino Civil Rights Movement" Sample Reel 13 min. (Box 3, Videotape 1)
  - "The Story of the Latino Civil Rights Movement" Sample Reel 13 min. (Box 3, Videotape 2)
  - "The Story of the Latino Civil Rights Movement" Sample Reel 13 min. (Box 3, Videotape 3)
  - Chicano! History of the Mexican American Civil Rights Movement "Taking Back the Schools" Epsiode #103 4/3/96 (Box 3, Videotape 4)
  - Chicano! History of the Mexican American Civil Rights Movement "Fighting for Political Power" Episode #104 4/3/96 (Box 3, Videotape 5)
  - Chicano! Episode 4 04/07/95 (Box 3, Videotape 6)
  - Chicano! History of the Mexican American Civil Rights Movement "The Struggle in the Fields" Episode #101 4/3/96 (Box 3, Videotape 7)
  - A New Civil Rights Movement Grows November 1994 (Box 3, Videotape 8)
  - City on the Edge (Box 3, Videotape 9)
  - Zaloom Mayfield Productions (Box 3, Videotape 10)
  - Chicano Moratorium March News (Box 3, Videotape 11)
  - Episode 2 D/V Received 12/21/95 (Box 3, Videotape 12)
  - Episode 1 50:23 Recieved 12/21/95 (Box 3, Videotape 13)
  - Episode 3 - "Blowouts" Revised 10/4/95 (Box 4, Videotape 1)
  - Episode 4 12/5 (Box 4, Videotape 2)
  - Episode 3 2/6/96 (Box 4, Videotape 3)
  - Episode 3 1/3/96 (Box 4, Videotape 4)
  - Ep. 4 2/8 (Box 4, Videotape 5)
  - In Search of Aztlan 1-23-01 (Box 4, Videotape 6)
  - "In Search of Aztlan" - Trailer/Approx. (Box 4, Videotape 7)
  - In Search of Aztlan - Sample Scenes (Box 4, Videotape 8)
  - Aztlan Project SAL 11/26 (Box 4, Videotape 9)
  - In Search of Aztlan - First Cut (2/01/01) (Box 4, Videotape 10)
  - In Search of Aztlan Temp Assembly 1-15-01 (Box 4, Videotape 11)
  - Aztlan Search Temp Cut 12/3 (Box 4, Videotape 12)
  - Those Whoe Came Before (Box 4, Videotape 13)
  - Aztlan 12-11-00 (Box 4, Videotape 14)
  - History's Mysteries Strange Disappearance of the Anasazi (Box 5, Videotape 1)
  - In Search for Aztlan (rough edit) (Box 5, Videotape 2)
  - A Docu-Comedy Work in Progress - Featuring Culture Clash "Search for Aztlan" (Box 5, Videotape 3)
  - Joseph Julian Gonzalez Music Cues In Search of Aztlan (Box 5, Videotape 4)
  - In Search of Aztlan - Oxy Viewing Tape (Box 5, Videotape 5)
  - "In Search of Aztlan" 1st Cut (Box 5, Videotape 6)
  - In Search of Aztlan (Box 5, Videotape 7)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 1: In Search of Aztlan Contracts & Agreements (Box 5, Cd-rom 8)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 1: In Search of Aztlan All Budget & Expense Files 1 of 1 (Box 5, Cd-rom 9)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 1: In Search of Aztlan All Website Files (Box 5, Cd-rom 10)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 1: In Search of Aztlan All Scripting And Proposal Files (Box 5, Cd-rom 11)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 1: In Search of Aztlan All Filming Files 1999-2004 (Box 5, Cd-rom 12)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 1: Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 1: In Search of Aztlan Transcripts & Interviews 1 of 2 (Box 5, Cd-rom 13)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 1: In Search of Aztlan Transcripts & Interviews 2 of 2 (Box 5, Cd-rom 14)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 1: In Search of Aztlan Editing & Post-Production (Box 5, Cd-rom 15)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 1: In Search of Aztlan All Publicity Files (Box 5, Cd-rom 15)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: Shot Lists Third Watch "To Project" Aug. 2002 (Back-up) (Box 5, Cd-rom 16)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: Shot Lists Miracles "To Protect" Sept. 2002 (Back up) (Box 5, Cd-rom 17)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: Retrospect Shot List (Box 5, Cd-rom 18)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: Shotlists: Voyager Day of Honor Voyager Retrospect DS9 Sons & Daughters Chicago Hope White Trash (Back up) (Box 5, Cd-rom 19)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: Shot Lists 1997/98 B5 "Objects in Motion" Voyager Retrospect" The Practice "Rhyme/Reason DS9 "The Reckoning" Voyager "Vis A Vis" Nash Bridges Lady Killer (Box 5, Cd-rom 20)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: Tru Calling "Daddy's Girl" Shot Lists Dec/Jan 2004 (Box 5, Cd-rom 21)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: Third Watch Shot List "Black & Blue" (Box 5, Cd-rom 22)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: The O.C. & Tarzan Shot Lists & Files (Box 5, Cd-rom 23)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: Crossing Jordan Files Misc. 2002-2004 (Box 5, Cd-rom 24)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: Shotlist Third Watch "Adam 553" Citizen Baines Resurrection Blvd Pelea Cholitas/Comenzando (Box 5, Cd-rom 25)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: Tru Calling Shot Lists Twas Night Befor Xmas (Box 5, Cd-rom 26)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: Tru Calling Shot Lists "Daddy's Girl" Backup (Box 5, Cd-rom 27)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 2: Third Watch "Black and Blue" Shotlists & Files (Box 5, Cd-rom 28)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 3: Shotlists: Badseed Carrier Dawson Heat (Box 5, Cd-rom 29)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 3: Story & Edit Files 1)Brimstone 2)Voyager 3)Thirdspace Interview (Back-up Copy) (Box 5, Cd-rom 30)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 3: Shots Lists: Brimstone: Carrier Crusade: Rules of the Game Voyager Synopsis B-5 Diary (Box 5, Cd-rom 31)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 3: Astronomy Files (Back-up) (Box 5, Cd-rom 32)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 3: Non-Fiction Articles 2000-2002 (back-up) (Box 5, Cd-rom 33)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 3: Shotlists: Smack is Back Voyager: Fair Trade Pretender Burning Zone (Box 5, Cd-rom 34)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 3: Shot List Stamese Dream (Box 5, Cd-rom 35)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 3: Voyager Seasons 1,2,3,4 Nash Bridges Deep Space Nine Babylon 5 Chicago Hope New York Undercover Space above and Beyond (Box 5, Cd-rom 36)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 3: Shot Lists: Burning Zone Chicago Hope: 2nd Chances (Box 5, Cd-rom 37)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 3: Shotlists: Resurrection Blvd. Mi Padre/Juntos/Sangre Strong Medicine History The Division Mothers Day RB/Suenos/The Court/Third (Box 5, Cd-rom 38)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 3: Shotlists ER/Resurrection Blvd. "A River in Egypt" Dos Padres/Dos Guardias Thirdwatch Falling (Box 5, Cd-rom 39)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 3: Resurrection Blvd. Shot Lists Pilot/Suenos/Dos Guardias (Box 5, Cd-rom 40)
  - Back-up Archive files Diskette Box 3: Other Spell-up Files (Nov. 5, 2002) (Box 5, Cd-rom 41)
  - A Showtime Original Series Resurrection Blvd. Volume 1 (Box 6, Volume 1)
  - A Showtime Original Series Resurrection Blvd. Volume two (Box 6, Volume 2)
  - Showtime Resurrection Blvd. (Box 6, Volume 3)
  - Disk Copies for Archive Box 4: Film/TV Treatments Chariada Pathfinder Milagro Refugee Rebote Yo Soy Chicano (Feature) (Box 7, Cd-rom 1)
  - Disk Copies for Archive Box 4: Last Americans Scripts Files 1999 (Box 7, Cd-rom 2)
  - Disk Copies for Archive Box 4: HBO Blowout Project (Backup) 1997-98 (Box 7, Cd-rom 3)
  - Disk Copies for Archive Box 4: Without Their Consent Facts & Treatment 2000-2001 (Box 7, Cd-rom 4)
  - Disk Copies for Archive Box 4: Hero Street Files 1997/98 (Backup (Box 7, Cd-rom 5)
  - Disk Copies for Archive Box 4: Brave Sea Files (Box 7, Cd-rom 6)
  - Disk Copies for Archive Box 4: Hero Street Files Salma Hayek Pitches (Box 7, Cd-rom 7)
  - Disk Copies for Archive Box 4: Brave Sea Microsoft Word Version 2000 (Box 7, Cd-rom 8)
  - Disk Copies for Archive Box 4: Chupacabra Caper/Valley of the Sun (Box 7, Cd-rom 9)
  - Disk Copies for Archive Box 4: Carmen Runs All Files WP & MW RD (Box 7, Cd-rom 10)
  - Disk Copies for Archive Box 4: At The Hands of Another All Files (Box 7, Cd-rom 11)
  - Disk Copies for Archive Box 4: Hoop Life Shot Lists (Box 7, Cd-rom 12)
  - Disk Copies for Archive Box 4: Arizona Homicide (Red Rum AZ) Files July 1, 2002 (Box 7, Cd-rom 13)
  - Back-up Files for Archives Diskette Box 5: Memoir Files (B) April 25, 1999 (Back-up) (Box 7, Cd-rom 14)
  - Back-up Files for Archives Diskette Box 5: Memoir Files (A) April 25, 1999 (Back-up) (Box 7, Cd-rom 15)
  - Back-up Files for Archives Diskette Box 5: Memoir First Ten Chapters Revised 6/01/98 (Backup) (Box 7, Cd-rom 16)
  - Back-up Files for Archives Diskette Box 5: Trevino Memoir Preface & Chapters 7-11 (Box 7, Cd-rom 17)
  - Back-up Files for Archives Diskette Box 5: Trevino drafts of Chapters 11,12 & 13 And "Add Pachuco" (Box 7, Cd-rom 18)
  - Back-up Files for Archives Diskette Box 5: Trevino Memoir Chapters 1-6 (Box 7, Cd-rom 19)
  - Back-up Files for Archives Diskette Box 5: All Memoir Files to 6/98 (Back up) (Box 7, Cd-rom 20)
  - Back-up Files for Archives Diskette Box 5: Memoir Early Drafts (Backup) (to 4/30/98 (Box 7, Cd-rom 21)
  - Back-up Files for Archives Diskette Box 5: Eyewitness Letters & Post-Publication Correspondence & Promotion 2001-2003 (Box 7, Cd-rom 22)
  - Back-up Files for Archives Diskette Box 5: Eyewitness Letters & Post-Publication Correspondence & Promotion 2001-2003 (Box 7, Cd-rom 23)
  - Back-up Files for Archives Diskette Box 5: Eyewitness Memoir Files off Laptop (7/01/02) (Box 7, Cd-rom 24)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 6: Salazar Inquest Transcripts (Box 7, Cd-rom 25)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 6: Chicano Files 1997/98 (Box 7, Cd-rom 26)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 6: TV Zombie Script (Box 7)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 6: Non-Fiction Articles & Speeches 1997/98 (Box 7, Cd-rom 28)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 6: Infinite Tomorrows Story Drafts 6/01/98 (Box 7, Cd-rom 29)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 6: Shot Lists Resurrection Blvd. "Regreso de" (Back-up) (Box 7, Cd-rom 30)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 6: Dancing with Carmen Miranda Arroyo Grande/The Valley and other Writings (Off Laptop 7/01/02 (Box 7, Cd-rom 31)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 6: Skyscraper that flew story Drafts 6/01/98 (Box 7, Cd-rom 32)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 6: Fabulous Sinkhole Completed Stories (Backup) (Box 7, Cd-rom 33)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 6: Skyscraper Files Back-Up (Nov. 5, 2002 (Box 7, Cd-rom 34)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 6: Sinkhole Files Back-Up (Nov. 5, 2002) (Box 7, Cd-rom 35)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 6: Return to Arroyo Grande Back-Up Files Nov. 5, 2002 (Box 7, Cd-rom 36)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 7: Non-Fiction Articles 2003-2006 (Box 7, Cd-rom 37)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 7: Letters of Recommendation (Box 7, Cd-rom 38)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 7: At the Hands of Another Files 1999-2003 (Box 7, Cd-rom 39)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 7: Trevino Notes on Other People's Scripts (Box 7, Cd-rom 40)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 7: Trevino Correspondence 2000-2004 (M-Z) (Box 7, Cd-rom 41)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 7: Trevino Correspondence 2000-2005 (A-L) (Box 7, Cd-rom 42)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 7: Correspondence 1997/98 (Backup) (Box 7, Cd-rom 43)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 7: DGA Files 1996/97/98 (Back up) (Box 7, Cd-rom 44)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 7: Chuytrevino.com 2004 Update Files (Box 7, Cd-rom 45)
  - Back-up Files for Archive Diskette Box 7: Aztlan Files off Laptop (7/01/02) (Box 7, Cd-rom 46)
  - Bello and Oye Publications (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Accession 2010-113, 0.25 Linear Feet
  - Movimiento!: draft, preface - p.30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Movimiento!: draft, p.31 - p.58 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Movimiento!: draft, p.59 - p.85 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Movimiento!: draft, p.86 - p.115 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Movimiento!: draft, p.116 - p.165 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Movimiento!: draft, p.166 - p.197 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Movimiento!: draft, p.198 - p.227 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Movimiento!: draft, p.228 - p.252 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Movimiento!: draft, p.253 - p.282 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Accession 2014-097
  - Directors Cuts
    - "Resurrection Blvd." Director's Cut Temp Pass 10/21/99 (Box 34, Videotape 1)
    - Resurrection Blvd. Ep. #40 "La Gran Pelea" Director's Cut (1st Pass) rt(67:00) For: Jesus Trevino (Box 34, Videotape 2)
    - EP. 510 "Begotten" CUTI - Pt. I Teaser Act II 11-14-96 (Box 34, Videotape 3)
    - SeaQuest "Good Soldiers" #K0405 PC 1 11/3/95 (Box 34, Videotape 4)
    - Ep. 510 "Begotten" Dir. Cut 11-19-96 (3:13) over (Box 34, Videotape 5)
    - Dir. Cut "Retrospect" (Box 34, Videotape 6)
    - Hardwood Productions Inc. "Hoop Life" Episode #8 Director's Cut (in progress) vis time code June 30/99 (Box 34, Videotape 7)
    - 162697 Sweet Justice "Fire" - Directors' Cut #2 (Box 34, Videotape 8)
    - Third Watch "To Protect..." #175-203 First Director's Cut 8/28/02 (Box 34, Videotape 9)
    - 57116 "Visit" 1st Cut (Box 34, Videotape 10)
    - 162697 Sweet Justice - "Fire" - 1st Cut 2/6/95 - 7 min. Long w/o scenes to come (Box 34, Videotape 11)
    - 57123 "Traitor" 1st Cut (Box 34, Videotape 12)
    - "Thirdspace" Director's Cut 6/26/97 (Box 34, Videotape 13)
    - NYPD Blue "Black Men Can Jump" 2-8-94 Director's Cut 1 (Box 34, Videotape 14)
    - "Hoop Life" Episode #10 Director's Cut July 22/99 (Box 34, Videotape 15)
    - "Miracles" - Ep. #103 - "Friendly Skies" Editor's Cut 9/25/02 (Box 34, Videotape 16)
    - Resurrection Blvd. Episode 20 "Juntos" Director's Cut Part 2 of 2 (Box 34, Videotape 17)
    - Que Manana sea Mejor (Box 34, Videotape 18)
    - seaQuest "The Siamese Dream" Episode #69723 Director's Cut 1 3/15/95 (Box 34, Videotape 19)
    - Birthwrite (Rough-Cut) (Box 34, Videotape 20)
    - seaQuest "The Sincerest Form of Flattery" #69708 Dir Cut 1 10/19/94 (Box 34, Videotape 21)
    - seaQuest The Sincerest Form of Flattery Episode #69708 Dir Cut 2 10/20/94 (Box 34, Videotape 22)
    - Running Dragon #76704 - "Birds of Paradise" Final Cut - 11/16/94 (Box 34, Videotape 23)
    - Running Dragon #76704 "Birds of Paradise" Editor's Cut #1 11/10/94 (Box 34, Videotape 24)
    - seaQuest "The Siamese Dream" Episode #69723 Director's Cut 2 3/16/95 (Box 34, Videotape 25)
    - The Burning Zone "Night Flight" #K1302 Editor's Cut TRT 48:18 (Box 34, Videotape 26)
    - Third Watch - #175-203 "To Protect..." Director's Cut Screen 9/3/02 (Box 34, Videotape 27)
    - Episode #204 "Tamara's Return" Director: Jesus Trevino Editor: Jan Northrop Director's Cut 9/24/98 (Box 34, Videotape 28)
    - "The Sincerest Form of Flattery" Episode #69708 First Cut 10/17/94 (Box 34, Videotape 29)
    - seaQuest "Good Soldiers" K0405 DC-1 Running time: 48:16 10/31/95 (Box 34, Videotape 30)
    - The Division (Box 34, Videotape 31)
    - Wilfrid's Special Christmas (Rough w/ Timecode) (Box 34, Videotape 32)
    - Third Watch Director's Cut #2 8/29/02 (Box 34, Videotape 33)
    - Interludes and Examinations Director's Cut Ep. 315 1/29/96 (Box 34, Videotape 34)
    - Third Watch "Falling" DC2 Cut For Jesus (Box 34, Videotape 35)
    - Third Watch: "Falling" ECI Output for Jesus Trevino (Box 34, Videotape 36)
    - 57123 2nd Cut (Box 34, Videotape 37)
    - "White Trash" 5M07 Director's Cut 10/14/97 (Box 34, Videotape 38)
    - Crusade "The Rules of the Game" Ep. 112 1/18/99 (Box 34, Videotape 39)
    - "Wilfrid's Special Christmas" First Cut (Box 34, Videotape 40)
    - Brimstone "Heat" #467452 Director's Cut (Box 34, Videotape 41)
    - Pretender "Curious Javod" Editor's Cut (Box 34, Videotape 42)
    - Stronge Medicine #201 "History" Avid Output 2/22/01 (Box 34, Videotape 43)
    - "A River in Egypt" Editor's Cut 12-17-01 (Box 34, Videotape 44)
    - Temp Color Timed Master "Heat" Brimstone 10/11/98 (Box 35, Videotape 1)
    - The Division - 'Mother's Day' Episode 005 Editor's Cut 12/09/00 (Box 35, Videotape 2)
    - New York Undercover "The Reckoning" Producer's Cut 2 Viewing Cassette Clean Picture 3/01/96 (Box 35, Videotape 3)
    - "Is it a crime?" Director's Cut 04/01/97 (Box 35, Videotape 4)
    - The Pretender: "Curious Javod" Director's Cut (Box 35, Videotape 5)
    - Grabiel's Fire Director's Cut 10/01/90 (Box 35, Videotape 6)
    - seaQuest "Brainlock" Director's Cut 9/20/95 (Box 35, Videotape 7)
    - New York Undercover "Is it a crime?" Viewing Cassette Clean Picture 4/17/97 (Box 35, Videotape 8)
    - Swift Justice Director's Cut #1 "Sex, Death, and Rock and Roll" 2/22/96 (Box 35, Videotape 9)
    - The Practice "Rhyme and Reason" Director's Cut 04/23/98 (Box 35, Videotape 10)
    - seaQuest "...Ice and Profit" Director's Cut 8/14/95 (Box 35, Videotape 11)
    - Darryl Tevis Directors Cut (Box 35, Videotape 12)
    - "Smack is Back" Director's Cut 10/3/96 (Box 35, Videotape 12)
    - New York Undercover "Is it a crime?" First Cut 03/27/97 (Box 35, Videotape 13)
    - DS9 #526 "Sons + Daughters" 7/30 (Box 35, Videotape 14)
    - DS9 #526 "Sons, Daughters" 7/31 (Box 35, Videotape 15)
    - The Court Ep 905 "Awing and a Prayer" Editor's Cut (Box 35, Videotape 16)
    - "White Trash" 5M07 Editor's Cut 10/13/97 (Box 35, Videotape 17)
    - "Second Chances" 4M19 Editor's Cut 3/5/97 (Box 35, Videotape 18)
    - "Second Chances" 4M19 Director's Cut 3/7/97 (Box 35, Videotape 19)
    - Third Watch: "To Protect" Editor's Cut 8-23-02 (Box 35, Videotape 20)
    - Wilfrid's Special Christmas (Rough) (Box 35, Videotape 21)
    - #179 Cut 2 (Box 35, Videotape 22)
    - Brimstone #467452 Director's Cut 9/29/98 "Heat" (Box 35, Videotape 23)
    - The Division 'Mother's Day' #005 Directors Cut 12/13/00 (Box 35, Videotape 24)
    - "Thirdspace" Director's Cut 6/20/97 (Box 35, Videotape 25)
    - Strong Medicine #201 "History" Director's Cut 2/23/01 (Box 35, Videotape 26)
    - Divided Loyalties Ep. #220 Director's Cut 4/06/95 (Box 35, Videotape 27)
    - "Objects in Motion" Ep. 521 Director's Cut 3-23-98 (Box 35, Videotape 28)
    - "Racing Mars" Episode 410 Director's Cut 12/17/96 (Box 35, Videotape 29)
    - "Racing Mars" Episode 410 Editor's Cut 12/13/96 (Box 35, Videotape 30)
    - Ep 179 "Concerning Flight" (Box 35, Videotape 31)
    - Voy #172 "Day of Honor" (7-12-97) (Box 35, Videotape 32)
    - Clennon does Marley on Kmex (12-18-96) (Box 35, Videotape 33)
    - The Search of Aztlan (Box 35, Videotape 34)
    - Deep Space 9 #545 "The Reckoning" Director's Cut 3-9-98 (Box 35, Videotape 35)
    - Ressurection Blv. Friday, July (9th Audition Final call back (Box 35, Videotape 36)
    - Resurrection Blvd. Ep. 031 "Mi Padre" Director's Cut For: Jesus Trevino (Box 35, Videotape 37)
    - Brimstone Dailies Director 4-255 (Box 35, Videotape 38)
    - DS9 #526 "Sons + Daughters" 7-28-97 (Box 35, Videotape 39)
    - Martial Law Ep. #110 Director's Cut Run Time - 55:46 w/ Gag Reel Avid Output 11-21-98 (Box 35, Videotape 40)
    - Voy #172 7-16-97 (Box 35, Videotape 41)
  - Documentaries
    - In Search of Aztlan (Box 36, Videotape 1)
    - Trevino Sample Reel Excerpts (Box 36, Videotape 2)
    - One out of Ten (1978) (Box 36, Videotape 3)
    - Soledad (1971) (Box 36, Videotape 4)
    - Somos Uno (1973) (Box 36, Videotape 5)
    - Raices de Sangre (1979) (Box 36, Videotape 6)
    - Denver Youth Conference - Reel One (1969) (Box 36, Videotape 7)
    - Carnalitos (Beta) (1973) (Box 36, Videotape 8)
    - Yo Soy (I Am) (Beta) (1985) (Box 36, Videotape 9)
    - Neighbors: The U.S. And Mexico (1985) (Box 36, Videotape 10)
    - Neighbors: The U.S. & Mexico (1985) (Box 36, Videotape 11)
    - Neighbors - US & Mexico (Beta) (1985) (Box 36, Videotape 12)
    - Galan Productions (Box 36, Videotape 13)
    - La Raza Unida (1972) (Box 36, Videotape 14)
    - In Search of Aztlan (Box 36, Videotape 15)
    - Yo Soy Chicano (1972) (Box 36, Videotape 16)
    - Los Mascarones (1972) (Box 36, Videotape 17)
    - Birthwrite (1989) (Box 36, Videotape 18)
    - Los Mascarones (1972) (Box 36, Videotape 19)
    - Seguin (1982) (Box 36, Videotape 20)
    - Yo Soy Chicano (Beta) (1985) (Box 36, Videotape 21)
    - Quinto Festival de Tenaz (1974) Teotihuacan, Mexico (Box 36, Videotape 22)
    - Best of Ahora (1970) (Box 36, Videotape 23)
    - "At One With" Trevino Interview (Beta) (1970) (Box 36, Videotape 24)
    - Presente: "Myths & Visions" (1982) (Box 36, Videotape 25)
    - Infinity Factory (1975) (Box 36, Videotape 26)
    - East LA Riots (Box 37, Videotape 1)
    - "Resurrection Blvd", April 26, 2011, Tape 1 "American Legion" Dir. Jesus Trevino (Box 37, Videotape 2)
    - Please Return to: Jesus Salvador Trevino Barrio Dog Productions (Box 37, Videotape 3)
    - El Teatro Campesino A.K.A. Pablo #2 A.K.A. Pablo #4 (Box 37, Videotape 4)
    - Tape #12 (Box 37, Videotape 5)
    - Promotional/Marketing Video "LatinosinHollywood.com" (Box 37, Videotape 6)
    - El Teatro Campesino (Box 37, Videotape 7)
    - Trevino Sampler Reel (Box 37, Videotape 8)
    - "Resurrection Blvd" April 26, 2001 "American Legion" 4-11-01 (Night Shoot) (Box 37, Videotape 9)
    - Trevino on Vistala. ABCLA (Box 37, Videotape 10)
    - Trevino Interview on KCET "Life and Times" (Box 37, Videotape 11)
    - Barrio Dog Production One Out of Ten 10/15/99 (Box 37, Videotape 12)
    - Jesus Trevino 02/27/04 "Ya Basta" (Box 37, Videotape 13)
    - "Carnalitos" (Box 37, Videotape 14)
    - Promotional/Marketing Video "LatinosinHollywood.com" (Box 37, Videotape 15)
- Accession 2014-098
  - Jesus Trevino Visual History 101 Disc 1 of 3 (Box 38, Disk 1)
  - Jesus Trevino Visual History 101 Disc 2 of 3 (Box 38, Disk 2)
  - Jesus Trevino Visual History 101 Disc 3 of 3 (Box 38, Disk 3)
  - Trevino Archives "Life and times" Interview (Box 38, Disk 4)
  - Jesus Trevino Latinopia roll #278 Interview Roll 1 (Box 38, Disk 5)
  - Jesus Trevino Latinopia roll #279 Interview Roll 2 (Box 38, Disk 6)
  - Jesus Trevino Latinopia roll #280 Interview Roll 3 (Box 38, Disk 7)
  - Jesus Trevino Latinopia roll #281 Interview Roll 4 (Box 38, Disk 8)